myvtu.com 2019-06-22

# Privacy and Policy - myVTU

Your privacy is critically important to us.

It is myVTU's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [myVTU](https://www.myvtu.com/). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this Privacy Policy to explain what information may be collected on our website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties, as one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our website. Depending on your activities when visiting our website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at info@myvtu.com

* * *

Like most website operators, myVTU collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. myVTU's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how myVTU's visitors use its website. From time to time, myVTU may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

myVTU also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. myVTU only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

* * *

Certain visitors to myVTU websites choose to interact with myVTU in ways that require myVTU to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that myVTU gathers depend on the nature of the interaction.

* * *

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

* * *

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by myVTU and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

* * *

myVTU discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that   
(i)need to know that information in order to process it on myVTU's behalf or to provide services available at myVTU's website, and   
(ii)myVTU will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, myVTU discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a court order or other governmental request, or when myVTU believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of myVTU, third parties or the public at large. 

If you are a registered user of myVTU and have supplied your email address, myVTU may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with myVTU and our products. We primarily use email notification to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. myVTU takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

* * *

myVTU may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. myVTU may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, myVTU does not disclose your personally-identifying information.

* * *

Like any other website, myVTU uses 'cookies'. These cookies are used to store information including visitors' preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users' experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors' browser type and/or other information. 

To enrich and perfect your online experience, myVTU uses "Cookies", similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. myVTU uses cookies to help myVTU identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.myvtu.com, and their website access preferences. myVTU visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using myVTU's websites, with the drawback that certain features of myVTU's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to myVTU's use of cookies.

* * *

Although most changes are likely to be minor, myVTU may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in myVTU's sole discretion. myVTU encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

* * *

myVTU follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

* * *

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
